上集回顾
Previously on Lost:
那飞机上装了海洛因
The plane was loaded with heroin.
他说他是在那边丛林发现的
He said he found it in the jungle.
丛林哪儿?
Where?
-不过是个雕像嘛  -仅仅是雕像吗?
-It's just a statue.  -Just a statue?
Charlie在哪儿?
Where is Charlie?
这是什么?
What's this?
这些是在你雕像里发现的
Because this was in your little statue.
我不知道
I didn't know.
如果是事前藏好的  我怎么会知道?
If it's sealed up inside a statue, how would I know?
你骗了我  Charlie
You lied to me.
听着  离我的孩子远点  明白吗?
I can't have you around my baby.
Claire Charlie  别再睡我们边上  明白吗?
Claire...I don't want you sleeping anywhere near us.
是百兽王!(一部美国动画片)
Voltron.
我的礼物在哪儿?
Where are my presents?
Charile  你的在这儿呢
Right over here, Charlie.
是一架钢琴!
It's a piano.
-是给我的吗?!  -是的  Charlie
-This is mine?  -Yes.
圣诞老人一定发现了你的天赋
Father Christmas must've known how talented you are.
亲爱的  你是天才
You're special, love.
总有一天你会带我们离开这儿
Someday you're gonna get us out of here.All of us.
来...
Now...
坐这儿  为我们弹一曲
Go on. Play us a tune.
弹吧  小弟弟
Come on, baby brother.
如果你不弹琴  你就救不了一家了
You can't save your family if you don't play.
来吧  Charlie
Come on, play.
弹一首  为我弹一首
Play me a tune.
来吧  让我们听听
Come on, now, let's hear it.
凭他  他当然救不了谁  音乐...
He ain't saving no one,he is. Music...
音乐哪儿都不能带你去  小Charlie
Music will never get you anywhere, Charlie boy.
你必须付出代价
You need a trade.
爸爸?
Dad?
弹吧  弟弟  救救我们
Do it, baby bro. Save us.
救救我们  Charlie
Save us, Charlie.
救救我们
Save us.
Aaron?
Aaron!
好了  Aaron  没事了
It's OK. It's all right.
Aaron!
Sun  Sun!
看到Claire和孩子了吗?  他们不见了
Sun. Have you seen Claire and the baby? They've gone.
他们就在那儿啊
They're right over there.
Aaron没事吧
Is Aaron OK?
当然  Charlie!
Yes, he's fine. Charlie, he's...
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：wjzhu校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：Linda  雯雯  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
早上我给Aaron做了些尿布
I made Aaron some nappies this morning.
我放在这儿
I'll just put those there.
谢谢你
Thanks.
他提到我了么?
Has he been asking about me?
Charlie  别这样
Charlie, don't.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我应该把雕像的事告诉你
I should have told you about the statue,
还有里面藏毒品的事
and what was in it.
我只是希望我们能像以前那样
I just wish things could get back to the way they were before.
可我们没有"以前"  Charlie
There is no "before. "
我们上了同一班飞机后才认识的
We were strangers on a plane and became friends.
现在Locke是你的朋友了?
Now Locke's your friend, huh?
Charlie  求你了
Please, Charlie.
从现在起  你让我静一静  好吗?
Just for now, give me some space, OK?
可以  静一下
Space.
再见了  伙计
See you, mate
好好照顾你妈妈  行吗?
Take care of your mum.
charlie?
你怎么你来啦?  你应该好好躺着
What are you doing up? You should be lying down.
我就想过来再看看她
I just needed to see her again
看她多漂亮
Isn't she brilliant?
是的  她美极了  Karen
She's beautiful, Karen.
我叫她Megan
I named her Megan.
Liam在哪儿?
Where's Liam?
他没来
He's not here.
Karen  这不关他的事
It wasn't his fault.
我们从Dresden的俱乐部过来
We were leaving Dresden.
我叫了辆出租  他开装行李的货车
I was in a cab. He was in a van with the gear.
去机场的路上他的车暴胎了
It blew a tyre on the way to the airport.
错过了飞机
He missed his flight.
他坐下一班飞机  马上就过来了
But he's on the next plane. He'll be here soon.
他没事吧?
But he's OK?
他很兴奋  做爸爸了
He's great. He's a dad.
怎么能...
For the...
Liam...
难以相信
Unbelievable.
Liam?
Liam  醒醒  嗨
Wake up. Hi!
你到底怎么了?
What the hell's wrong with you?
你究竟做了些什么啊?
What the hell are you doing?
你来啦
Baby brother.
你不是早戒了嘛
You're supposed to be cleaning up.
快起来
Get up.
我跟Karen说你只是错过了飞机
I told Karen you missed your flight.
她一个人在医院  你却在这儿吸毒  你到底怎么啦?
She's alone at the hospital and you're here fixing.
我很好  很好
I'm cool.
我只是需要恢复正常  仅此而已
I just needed to get right, that's all.
别担心  我也给你留了点
Don't worry. I left you some.
恢复?
Get right?
为什么还不起来?
Why don't you get up?
洗个澡  换件衣服  马上去医院
Take a shower, get dressed, get to the hospital?
好啦  好啦  我知道了   马上就做
All right. I'm on it.
对了
By the way,
生的是女孩儿
you have a daughter
她叫Megan
Her name's Megan.
跟她妈妈姓?
After Mum?
是的  随她妈妈
After Mum.
好好洗洗吧你
Now clean yourself up.
你现在也是他妈的父亲了
You're a sodding father now.
慢慢来  很好
Easy. That's good. That was good.
好的  我们再来一次
One more.
Sawyer  你在岛那头的时候
Sawyer. When you were over there across the island,
跟那边的人熟么?
how well did you get to know those Tailies?
当然  怎么了?
Well enough. Why?
有个叫Libby的看起来不错
That Libby chick seems pretty cool.
我是说  她人还不错吧?
I mean, is she?
Jabba  看起来你看上人家啦?
You got a little love connection brewing over there, Jabba?
没有  随便问问而已
No. I'm just asking.
是啊  随便问问
I hear you asking.
算了
Forget it.
搞什么你?  看起来你像个初中生
What's with you? You're acting like you're in junior high.
哦  瞧那儿
What do we have here?
看起来Ana Lucia找到了个不错的向导
Ana Lucia's getting the $20 tour.
这是我第三次看到他们从里边出来了
That's the third time I've seen them walking out of the jungle.
你觉得他们在里边干吗呢?
What do you suppose they're doing?
Sawyer  专心做你的练习
You just do your exercises.
该死的
Bloody hell.
是个孩子
The baby.
来人啊
Help.
快来人  孩子掉水里了!
The baby.
Aaron!
我来了  Aaron  我来了
I'm coming. It's OK.
没事  没事儿的
Just hang on.
现在安全了
I got you.
我在这儿  没事的  没事  你安全了
It's all right. It's OK. You're OK now.
好了  好了  你安全了
You're safe.
没事儿了
It's OK.
妈妈?
Mum?
Claire?
他有危险  你必须去救他
He's in danger. You have to save him.
那孩子非常危险 Charlie  只有你能救他
You have to save the baby.Only you can save him
孩子有危险  孩子  Charlie 你得去救他
You have to save the baby.
Charlie  只有你能救他 你得去救他  你必须去
charlie?
你在这儿干吗?
Only you can save him. What are you doing?
你在干什么  伙计?
What are you doing, man?
出什么事了?
What's going on?
已经是深夜了  你抱着孩子在那干吗?
What are you doing with the baby?
我不知道
I don't know.
来人啊  有人偷了我的孩子!
Help. Somebody took my baby.
Claire  出什么事了?
我不知道  Aaron不见了
I don't know. Aaron's gone.
没事  我们在这儿
It's OK. We're over here.
孩子没事儿吧?  他还好吧?!
Is he all right?
Claire...
我不清楚发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
他很好  我做了一个梦
He's OK, though. I had this dream...
不要了?
Stick?
不是玩21点吗?  我以为你还会要的
I don't know, dude. Don't I need 21? I think I should hit.
如果拿到6  我就暴了
But I got a six. I'm gonna bust.
你怎么知道你会暴?
How do you know that?
我不清楚  但你在想我要暴了
I don't. But you gotta assume that I'm gonna bust.
为什么?
Why?
看看是谁正要去洗衣服呢
Well, well, look who's off to the Laundromat.
快去啊
Go on.
我想你肯定也有衣服要洗吧  Jethro?
I'm sure you've got a load you need to drop in, Jethro.
我在等待时机
I'm kind of waiting for my moment.
那么...
Well...
你的机会来了  Hoss
Your moment is now, Hoss.
嘿  Libby
Hey, Libby.
你一个人啊
Hey, yourself.
你好  John
Hey, John.
能和你谈谈么?
Talk to you for a second?
好  什么事  Charlie?
What is it? Charlie?
我想你已经知道昨晚发生的事了吧?
I take it you heard about what happened last night?
你是说你半夜里把Claire的孩子偷走的事
You taking the baby out of Claire's tent in the middle of the night?
是的  我听说了
I heard.
整件事就是个误会  John  当时我在梦游
It was a big misunderstanding. I was sleepwalking.
我也不知道怎么了
I don't know how or why.
你想我帮什么忙呢  Charlie?
Is there something you want from me??
我想你替我跟Claire解释一下
I was hoping you could speak to Claire for me.
你懂的  帮我说点好话
Put in a good word.
你还在碰那东西吗?
Are you using?
什么?
What?
海洛因  你还在吸毒么?
Heroin. Are you using again?
Kate看到一只马  有吗
Kate sees a horse, nothing.
几乎每天都有人看到Walt在丛林里晃荡
Pretty much everybody's seen Walt in the jungle.
怎么轮到我  就肯定是因为吸毒的原因呢?
When it's Charlie, it must be the drugs.
好吧  你还没正面回答我呢
It's funny, you didn't answer the question.
还记得那驾飞机吗  John?
You remember the plane?
我和Eko把它烧了
We burned it. Eko and me.
我们把一切都烧掉了  包括海洛因  还有那些雕像
We burned the whole thing. The heroin, the statues.
都没了  销毁了
It's all gone, destroyed.
全部么?
All of them?
当然
All of them.
失去的信任是很难找回来的
Trust is a hard thing to win back.
Claire还需要时间
Claire needs time.
你得让他们母子静一静
You should leave her and the baby alone for a while.
你还好吧?  你脸色很差
Can you do this? You look green.
滚开  我很好
Sod off. I'm fine.
好的  我们再来一遍
Let's give this another go, shall we?
那好  振作起来好吗?  免得你忘记  我们就得这样
Get it together. Lest you forget, we need this.
给我杯茶
Tea.
你们准备好了么?
So, you lads ready?
当然  我们准备好了
We're ready. Let's go.
这次别演砸了  行么?
Let's try not to blow it this time.
谢了  你还好吧 没问题
You good?
我们还有二十分钟
We've only 20 minutes till we're in overtime.
现在  各就各位  准备好
Get it right.
留心你的拖鞋
知道了
All right.
摄像
Camera.
转向八点钟方向 举高点
Rotate on the eight count. Rolling.
都把产品举起来
Hold the product up.
"好伙伴纸尿布"  第53场
Butties diapers, take 53.
转回去  准备
Playback.Mark it.
开始!
And action.
像...
Acting like...
停!
Cut.
没事儿
It's all right.
就这样  收工!
That's it. We're wrapped.
等等  伙计  等等!
No. Mate. Hang on.
等等
Wait.
等等  你这是什么意思?
What are you doing?
我们别浪费时间了
Let's not waste any more time.
用你们已经是给你们律师面子了
You were only hired as a favour to your lawyer.
我找Dirt Spigot
I wanted Dirt Spigot.
得了  伙计
Come on, mate.
再给我们一次机会
Give us another chance.
你想再来一次吗?  那就听我的
You want another chance? Take my advice.
甩掉他  他是害群之马
Ditch that one. He's a bloody disaster.
我不会丢下任何一个
I'm not ditching anyone.
他是我兄弟
He's my brother.
好吧  那这样
Right. Well, then,
我想你被解雇了
I guess you're fired.
这儿就洗衣机和干衣机还不错了  是吧?
Is this washer and dryer newer than everything else in here?
对我来说  只要能洗就行
It washes clothes. That's all I need to know.
总算
Finally.
有人觉得这事容易了
Someone who keeps it simple.
看这件衣服
Look at this.
我在一个没人要的皮箱里找到的
I got it in some of the abandoned luggage.
你觉得我穿了好看么?
You think I can pull this off?
让我给你点提示
Let me give you a hint.
通常如果一个女孩这样问
When a girl asks that kind of question,
那她就是想得到称赞
she's looking for validation.
我们...之前见过么?
Do I know you from somewhere?
你指除了在飞机上之外?
You mean other than the flight?
飞机上... 好了  转过身去
The flight... Turn around.
转过去  转过去  我想试试这件衣服
Turn around. I'm gonna try it on.
-好吧  尽管试  -不许偷看
-Sure, go ahead.  -No peeking.
我不敢相信你忘了曾经踩过我的脚
I cannot believe you don't remember stepping on my foot.
-是么?  -当然咯  而且还踩的很痛
-I did?  -Yes, you did. And it was hard.
我记得你因为你是最后一个上飞机的
I remember you were the last one on the flight,
你急急忙忙全身是汗  还戴着耳机
and you were all sweaty and you had headphones on
喀一声
and crunch,
然后你就踩了我
you stepped on my foot.
好了  转过来吧
Turn around.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
太好看了
It's awesome.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
给树做记号
I'm marking trees.
为什么?
Why?
因为...
Because
这些是我的爱好
these are the ones I like.
你告诉Locke我拿了飞机上的雕像么?
Did you tell Locke you gave me a statue from the plane?
我为什么要那样做?
Why would I do that?
可他知道了  伙计
He knows, man.
那个秃子好像知道了什么
That bald wanker knows something.
出什么问题了  Charlie?
Is something wrong?
除了有点失控之外  别的还行
Apart from me losing my mind? No. Everything's peachy.
为什么你说你有点失控呢?
Why would you say you are losing your mind?
要不怎么会梦游
How about the fact that I've been sleepwalking?
半夜把孩子抱走...
Stealing babies from their cribs?
还有真实不能再真实的梦
And the vivid dreams that make me feel like I'm awake
直到醒来才发现是假的
until, of course, I wake up.
你都梦到了什么?
What are your dreams about?
各种有关Aaron遇险的事...
Variations of Aaron being in mortal peril.
困在钢琴里
Trapped in a piano.
漂浮在大海里...
Drifting out to sea.
还有一只鸽子
There's the flying dove,
Claire和我的妈妈穿的像个天使 并告诉我要我去救那个孩子
and Claireand my mum dressed as angels telling me I need to save the baby.
怎么了?
What?
你是否想过这些梦有某些含义?
Have you ever considered that these dreams mean something?
例如?
Like what?
假如你真应该去保护那个孩子呢?
What if you do need to save the baby?
我有话要跟她说
I have to talk to her.
不  我现在一定要跟她说  她会听的
She'll wanna hear this.
-你知道什么了?告诉我 我转告她  -Kate 不 不 Claire!
-Tell me and I will tell her.  -Kate,no,no, Claire!
Claire  听我说
Please.
-Aaron有危险  -你说什么?
-Aaron's in danger.  -What?
孩子有危险!  听着 我一直在做那个梦 我知道那意味着什么
The baby's in danger.I've been having these dreams.I know what they mean now.
Claire  听着  我们必须给Aaron作个洗礼
We have to baptise Aaron.
-什么?  -我们可以做的  Eko就是个神父
-What?  -We can do this. Eko's a priest.
－我们可以做的   －说完了吧  说完了就走吧
-We can do this.  -You've said your piece.It's time for you to go.
不  等等  我不能走  Claire  我们必须给Aaron做洗礼!
Wait. We have to baptise Aaron.
Claire  孩子有危险  我们必须这么做  必须!
He's in danger. We've got to do this.
给  下雨的时候用的着
Here. For when it rains.
谢谢
Thanks.
你打算什么时候告诉我丛林里发生了什么?
When are you gonna tell me what happened in the jungle?
我已经说了
I already did.
拉紧点否则会松的
Pull it tighter, or it'll sag.
你只告诉我那家伙说了什么
You told me what that guy said.
你还没说你为什么要返回那儿
You didn't tell me what made you turn around.
为什么你又回来了
What made you come back.
他拿枪指着Kate的头
He had a gun at Kate's head.
你反感那样?
You hitting that?
你什么意思?
What?
飞机失事...你们却活下来了...
Plane crash. You both survived.
美丽的沙滩...
Nice beach. She's hot, you're hot.
她很热情你也一样  是人都会这么做的
She's hot, you're hot.That's what people do.
我并非"反感那样"
I'm not "hitting that. "
Karen把我甩了
Karen kicked me out, man.
什么?
What?
发生什么事了?
What happened?
她...
她觉得跟我在一起没有安全感
She thinks I'm dangerous.
她为什么会那么想?
Why would she think that?
因为我冷谈了她
Because I dropped her.
我抛弃了Megan
I dropped Megan.
Liam  没事儿的
Liam, it's all right.
我没钱  什么都没有
We've got no money.We've got nothing.
我们能干什么?
What are we gonna do?
-我们能熬过去的  -怎么熬?
-We'll get through this.  -Yeah? How's that?
我又开始写歌了
I'm writing again.
我写了首新歌
I got a new song.
是关于兄弟的
It's about two brothers.
两个本应做屠夫的兄弟
Who should've been butchers.
别这么说  这是首好歌
Don't say that. This is a good one.
我觉得会一鸣惊人
I feel like this might be the one
好了  先听听
Listen to this.
真滑稽
Nice, man.
你发现我站在这儿
真可笑
我在雨中哭泣
就这样
我们永不言败
振作起来
我们能生存下来
不错吧
This could work.
肯定能红
It's good,
不错吧? 我们能办到的
right? We could make it work.
就像过去一样写歌
Write all night, just like the old days.
恩  然后呢?
So,
好兄弟
baby brother,
你还有那个（海洛因）吗?
you got any?
我对你很失望  Charlie
I'm disappointed in you.
你跟踪我?
You followed me?
你来这里多久了?
How long you been coming out here?
John  你误会了
You've got the wrong idea, man.
你说你把海洛因全部销毁了  结果呢  这还有
You said you destroyed them and yet here they are.
这也是个误会吗?
我来就是为了销毁它们的  我就要这么做了
I came to finish the job, to get rid of these.
被我发现了  你当然就这么说啦
Very convenient, now that I've found them.
你打算怎么做?
What are you doing?
我已经给你机会了
There was a time when I let you choose
让你选择你是否还需要它们
whether or not you were gonna do this to yourself.
现在  让我帮你下决心
Now I'm making that choice for you.
你不相信我?
You don't believe me?
给我  给我  看...我现在就销毁他们!
Give them to me right now. I'll destroy them.
我把它们全扔了  让它们随这鬼风飘走!
I'll throw them in the sodding wind.
听着  John  我知道我撒谎了 好吧?
Look, John,I know I lied, all right?
等等  你等等  John
Just wait.
记得我们说过什么吗?
Remember all those talks we had?
你跟我说过
You and me?
在这里发生的任何一件事 都有一个理由
You said everything happens for a reason.
这个岛正在考验我们
This island tests us.
这就是一个  John  一个考验 是对我的考验  这就是海洛因还在这的原因
That's what this is. This is my test. That's why these are here.
那是因为你把它们藏在这里了  Charlie
These are here because you put them here.
不  等等  John  等等
Wait.
你到哪儿去?
What are you gonna do?
你打算告诉Claire?
Are you gonna tell Claire?
不可以
You can't.
如果她看到这些  我就完了
If she sees them, I'm done.
她再也不会相信我了  而她现在需要信任我  John
She'll never trust me again, and she has to.
都是为了孩子  对吧?
It's about the baby.
Aaron有危险
Aaron's in danger.
你必须相信我
You have to believe me.
你自己放弃了被人信任的权利  Charlie
You've given up the right to be believed.
我们的小男孩怎么样了?
Hi.How's our boy?
他很好
He's good.
John  我能问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you something?
当然
Sure.
你是否相信
Do you think Aaron and I
我和Aaron能在机舱里待着么?
could stay in the bedroom in the hatch for a while?
每隔一个半小时就会有很吵报警声
Alarm goes off every hour and a half.
不适合婴儿在那儿过夜
It's not the best place for a baby to sleep through the night.
当然
Yeah, sure.
要不我把帐篷搬过来
How about if I move my stuff down here,
就靠着你的帐篷
set up right next to your tent?
如果能那样最好了  谢谢你
That'd be great. Thanks.
好  就这么定了
Then consider it done.
John  你是否了解
You don't know anything about baptism,
你是否了解有关洗礼的事?
do you?
不是很了解  怎么了?
Not a whole lot. Why?
Charlie之前来我的这儿并且...
Charlie came by my tent before.
他说Aaron必须要接受洗礼...
He told me Aaron had to be baptised.
因为他有危险
That he was in danger.
我的理解是洗礼能保证无论发生什么
My understanding is baptism is about making sure children get into heaven,
小孩子将来都能进天堂
should anything happen.
因此称为"精神保险"
Call it spiritual insurance.
这儿很安全  Claire
There isn't any danger.
Charlie只是...
Charlie just...
Charlie只是感觉他有义务保护孩子
Charlie just feels like he has to save the baby
因为他无法保护自己
because he can't save himself.
晚上见
I'll see you tonight.
好的
OK.
Charlie  能帮我们一把吗?
Charlie, can you give us a hand?
现在不行  Sayid
Now's not a good time, Sayid.
我们把它抬起来
Let's lift this.
好的  搞定了
Okay,I got it. I got it.
着火了  着火了!
Fire.Fire.
拿上工具  还有盛沙子的  还有其他能带的
Grab tools, containers for sand, anything you have.
如果现在不扑灭  火会烧到营地这儿的!
If we don't stop it now, it'll burn right through the camp.
在这儿看好Aaron
Stay here with Aaron.
我们需要从这儿把火势切断!
We need to cut a fire break right here.
保证一个桶的距离!
Form a bucket line.
带上一些人  去弄点水!
Some of you people, down to the water.
Sawyer!
我们会处理的  在这等着!
You're heading them off. Right here.
Liam?!
我的钢琴
My piano.
发生...出什么事了?
What's going on?
Liam
我的钢琴呢?
Where's my piano?
我卖了
I sold it.
什么?
You what?
-等等  -别管我
-Wait.  -Get off me.
那钱呢?  又去买毒品了?!
Where's the money? Is it up your sodding arm?
我没有  我已经两天不吸了
I'm clean. I haven't used in two days.
两天?  真该恭喜你啊!
Two days? Happy anniversary.
那你多就不碰了?
How long you been clean?
钱到哪儿去了?
Where's the money?
她要离开我
She was gonna leave me.
Charlie  她想把Megan带走
She was gonna take Megan.
你打算怎么办  Liam?
What did you do?
Karen在澳洲有个叔叔
Karen's got an uncle in Australia.
他能给我一份工作
He's gonna get me a job.
悉尼有个戒毒中心
There's a rehab clinic in Sydney.
我们需要去那儿的钱
I just needed the money to get us there.
我不得不这么做
I have to do this.
为了她们母女  为了我的家庭
I have to take care of myself, for them, for my family.
我必须好起来
我也是你的家人啊!
I'm your family.
再等等  你就不能再等等吗?
Wait. Will you just wait?
我再也不能等了  Charlie
I can't.
你走了乐队怎么办?  那首歌怎么办?
What about the band? What about the song?
请你理解  我必须走
Try to understand. I have to go.
必须
I have to.
好吧  事情安顿好之后我会联络你的
I'll give you a call when things settle down for me.
都为你?  那我呢?
For you? What about me?
我的家庭怎么办?
What about my family?
我的家怎么办?
Charlie!  你在干什么?!
What are you doing?
我必须这么做!  他带走了我的孩子!
I'm doing what I have to do. He's got my baby.
-住手!  -不!Claire  没事儿的!
-Stop it.  -It's all right.
-Charlie  住手!  -这不是... 不!我...
-Help! Help!  -It's not...
救命啊! 来人啊! 来人啊! 他抢了我的孩子!
Somebody, help! He's got my baby!
来人啊!
Come on,
够了  Charlie  求求你了
please.
别这么做
Stop.
我只想救他!
I just want to save him.
Charlie!  够了! 求求你!
-Charlie!  -It's all right.
把孩子给我
Give me the baby.
Eko  告诉他们!  都告诉他们Eko!
Eko, tell them.
告诉他们你跟我说的那些  你说孩子必须接受洗礼!
Tell them what you told me. That the baby has to be baptised.
不是这种方式
This is not the way.
Charlie...
来  把孩子给我
Give him to me.
你以为你是谁  John?!
Who the hell are you?
Aaron的事跟你无关!
Aaron's not your responsibility.
他出生的时候你在哪儿?!
Where were you when he was born?
他出事儿的时候你又在哪里?!
When he was taken?
你不是他的父亲
You're not his father.
你和他不是一家人!
You're not his family.
你也不是  Charlie
Neither are you.
我必须做  我知道
I have to do this. I need to.
我不想伤害他
I'm not gonna hurt him.
可你伤害了我  Charlie
You're hurting me.
Claire.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你得缝一下
You need stitches.
忍一下
Try to be still.
火是我放的  Jack
I started the fire.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我太绝望了  她不...
I was desperate.
我需要知道你再也不会干这种傻事儿了
I need to know you're never gonna do anything like this again.
再也不
Ever.
我知道后果
I know what this looks like,
人们会怎么想
what people think.
这都不重要了  但是...
It doesn't matter now,
我没吸毒
but I didn't use.
我很想
I wanted to.
我真的很想
I really wanted to.
但我忍住了
But I didn't.
这不是我关心的  Charlie
That's not what I asked.
不会再发生了
It's not gonna happen again.
Charlie告诉我你是个神父
Charlie told me you're a priest.
是的
他说是你告诉他的  我必须...
He said you told him that I had to have...
我没有让Charlie那样做
I did not tell Charlie to do what he did.
他误解了这我很抱歉
I'm sorry if he misunderstood me.
但你是否也认为这孩子必须接受洗礼?
But do you think the baby has to be baptised?
你知道洗礼是什么吗?
Do you know what baptism is?
它可以让你进入天堂
It's what gets you into heaven.
施洗约翰给耶稣洗礼时
It is said that when John the Baptist baptised Jesus,
天堂开了
the skies opened up
一只鸽子从天空中飞下来
and a dove flew down from the sky.
它告诉约翰
This told John something,
他已经帮这个人洗净了所有的罪孽
that he had cleansed this man of all his sins,
约翰释放了他
that he had freed him.
天堂最终还是接纳了他
Heaven came much later.
我没被洗礼过
I haven't been baptised.
是不是说如果你给Aaron做洗礼
Does that mean if you do it to Aaron
一旦发生了什么事
and something happened to us,
我跟她就不能在一起了?
that we wouldn't be together?
如果你们都接受洗洗了就没事了
Not if I baptise you both.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====